

MARIAH FESER

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER

About Me

I am thrilled to be in the world of development as a graduate of a fullstack coding program through University of Toronto. My previous experience of owning, operating and selling a business in the beauty industry has taught and instilled the importance of the customer service, that benefits in any business setting. This knowledge of how vital the customer experience is will provide value to the development of any web application for both the users and developers.

EXPERIENCE

BUSINESS OWNER

MicroBeauty Studio

2016 - Present

- Day-to-day operations of running studio
- Managing employees and client coordinations
- Client services
- · Educational programs

HOTEL OWNER

Escal Acres

2020 - 2022

- · Managing of small boutique rentals in Costa Rica
- Guest services that include cleaning, communication, excursions
- · Hiring and management of staff
- Administrative role

SERVICE

Cactus Club Cafe

2009 - 2016

- Food service
- Customer service and experience
- Collaboration with team
- · Organization and working in timely manner

604-690-3010

Feser.mk@gmail.com

1940 Sunflower Road, Christina Lake

<u>Linked in profile click here</u>

EDUCATION

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT

University of Toronto

2023

COSMETIC TATTOO ARTIST

Phi Academy

2016

PSYCHIATRIC NURSING

Douglas College

2011-2013

SECONDARY SCHOOL

Sands Secondary School

2007 - 2011

SKILLS

- Web Design
- Agile Methodology
- Full-Stack Development
- Problem-Solving
- Customer experience
- · Hotel Management
- Strong Communication
- Organizational skills